{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "餐厅",
      "answer": "Cāntīng | dining hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "在",
      "answer": "Zài | to be (here, there), to be (in, on, at)"
    },
    {
      "question": "哪儿",
      "answer": "Nǎr | where"
    },
    {
      "question": "请问",
      "answer": "Qǐngwèn | may i ask...？"
    },
    {
      "question": "问",
      "answer": "wèn | to ask"
    },
    {
      "question": "这",
      "answer": "Zhè | this"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿舍",
      "answer": "Sùshè | dormitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "女",
      "answer": "Nǚ | female"
    },
    {
      "question": "学生",
      "answer": "Xuéshēng | student"
    },
    {
      "question": "进",
      "answer": "Jìn | to enter"
    },
    {
      "question": "坐",
      "answer": "Zuò | to sit"
    },
    {
      "question": "谢谢",
      "answer": "Xièxiè | to thank"
    },
    {
      "question": "对不起",
      "answer": "Duìbùqǐ | I'm sorry"
    },
    {
      "question": "我",
      "answer": "Wǒ | I, me"
    },
    {
      "question": "知道",
      "answer": "Zhīdào | to know"
    },
    {
      "question": "没关系",
      "answer": "Méiguānxì | never mind, it doesn't matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "好",
      "answer": "Hǎo | good, well, fine, OK"
    },
    {
      "question": "再见",
      "answer": "Zàijiàn | goodbye"
    },
    {
      "question": "再",
      "answer": "Zài | again"
    }
  ]
}
